<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Fallen Angels</title>
    <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Fallen Angels</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Fallen Angels, Inc.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:33:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Armenian Pavilion at Venice Biennale 2026</title>
      <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/venicebiennale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:33:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/venicebiennale/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;zadik-zadikian-to-represent-armenia&#34;&gt;Zadik Zadikian to Represent Armenia&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fallen Angels Inc. is honored to announce that the Republic of Armenia will be represented at the 2026 Venice Biennale by artist Zadik Zadikian, whose visionary practice spans decades of sculptural innovation and a lifelong dialogue with material, light, and the metaphysics of artistic making. In alignment with the Biennale&amp;rsquo;s curatorial theme &lt;em&gt;In Minor Keys&lt;/em&gt;—an invitation to create spaces of reflection, resonance, and poetic attunement—Zadikian will transform the Armenian Pavilion into a living, breathing studio: a site of continual making, presence, and shared experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cafesjian Center for the Arts - Yerevan - Fall 2024 Show</title>
      <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/ccfa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:33:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/ccfa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;fallen-angels-monument---coming-in-fall-2024&#34;&gt;Fallen Angels Monument - Coming in Fall 2024&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Layering Reason&lt;/strong&gt; - is a monument by artist Zadik Zadikian as a dedication from the Armenian community to the fallen soldiers of the 2020 war in Nagorno-Karabakh that took the lives of thousands of Armenian soldiers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For Armenians around the globe, this is a tragic topic. The goal of this monument is to immortalize the fallen soldiers and give the viewer a visceral experience of the scale of loss inflicted by the conflict. Along with this, the piece aims to be a work of hope.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
