<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fallen Angels</title>
    <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fallen Angels</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Fallen Angels, Inc.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:33:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fallenangelsproject.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Armenian Pavilion at Venice Biennale 2026</title>
      <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/venicebiennale/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 15:33:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/venicebiennale/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;zadik-zadikian-to-represent-armenia&#34;&gt;Zadik Zadikian to Represent Armenia&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fallen Angels Inc. is honored to announce that the Republic of Armenia will be represented at the 2026 Venice Biennale by artist Zadik Zadikian, whose visionary practice spans decades of sculptural innovation and a lifelong dialogue with material, light, and the metaphysics of artistic making. In alignment with the Biennale&amp;rsquo;s curatorial theme &lt;em&gt;In Minor Keys&lt;/em&gt;—an invitation to create spaces of reflection, resonance, and poetic attunement—Zadikian will transform the Armenian Pavilion into a living, breathing studio: a site of continual making, presence, and shared experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cafesjian Center for the Arts - Yerevan - Fall 2024 Show</title>
      <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/ccfa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:33:57 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fallenangelsproject.org/posts/ccfa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;fallen-angels-monument---coming-in-fall-2024&#34;&gt;Fallen Angels Monument - Coming in Fall 2024&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Layering Reason&lt;/strong&gt; - is a monument by artist Zadik Zadikian as a dedication from the Armenian community to the fallen soldiers of the 2020 war in Nagorno-Karabakh that took the lives of thousands of Armenian soldiers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For Armenians around the globe, this is a tragic topic. The goal of this monument is to immortalize the fallen soldiers and give the viewer a visceral experience of the scale of loss inflicted by the conflict. Along with this, the piece aims to be a work of hope.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fallenangelsproject.org/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fallen Angels&lt;/strong&gt; is a nonprofit organization committed to elevating Armenian culture on the global stage through the power of art. Our mission is to deepen awareness, understanding, and appreciation of Armenia’s rich cultural heritage—both across the worldwide Armenian diaspora and within the broader international arts community. Through exhibitions, artistic collaborations, and cultural initiatives, we champion creative expression as a bridge between communities and a catalyst for shared democratic values.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We support artists, institutions, and educational programs that foster dialogue and cross-cultural exchange, ensuring that Armenian voices remain vibrant, visible, and influential within today’s cultural landscape. In this spirit, Fallen Angels is honored to lead and support major international projects such as the Armenian Pavilion at the Venice Biennale 2026, advancing Armenia’s artistic innovation at one of the most significant and respected cultural platforms in the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fallenangelsproject.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get in Touch&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We welcome inquiries from donors, artists, institutions, and cultural organizations interested in supporting or collaborating with Fallen Angels Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;general-inquiries&#34;&gt;General Inquiries&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For general information about our programs, partnerships, or donation opportunities:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@fallenangels.org&#34;&gt;info@fallenangels.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;leadership&#34;&gt;Leadership&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aram Zadikian&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Executive Director&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Phone:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;tel:+13234041152&#34;&gt;+1 323-404-1152&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;mailing-address&#34;&gt;Mailing Address&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fallen Angels Inc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;9355 La Tuna Canyon Rd&#xA;Los Angeles, California&lt;br&gt;&#xA;United States&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-our-organization&#34;&gt;About Our Organization&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fallen Angels Inc. is a registered 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization (EIN available upon request). We are committed to transparency and welcome questions about our mission, projects, and financials.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>https://fallenangelsproject.org/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fallenangelsproject.org/donate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;support-our-mission&#34;&gt;Support Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fallen Angels Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; is a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization dedicated to elevating Armenian culture on the global stage through the power of art. Your tax-deductible donation helps us support major international projects, including the Armenian Pavilion at the Venice Biennale 2026 and other critical cultural initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tax-deductible-contributions&#34;&gt;Tax-Deductible Contributions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a registered 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization, all donations to Fallen Angels Inc. are tax-deductible to the fullest extent permitted by law. Our Federal Tax ID (EIN) is available upon request.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
